{
    "subject": "Rick_Rubin",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Tougher_Than_Leather__film_",
    "human_readable": "Rick Rubin directed the film Tougher Than Leather.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9822575449943542,
            "question": "Has Rick Rubin directed other films besides Tougher Than Leather?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9191195964813232,
            "question": "Who directed the film Tougher Than Leather?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7505576610565186,
            "question": "Is Rick Rubin known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7011582851409912,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Rick Rubin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6956247687339783,
            "question": "What genre is the film Tougher Than Leather?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593886613845825,
            "question": "Where was Tougher Than Leather filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5871748328208923,
            "question": "What film did Rick Rubin direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5456992983818054,
            "question": "What year was Tougher Than Leather released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5010122656822205,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Tougher Than Leather?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49504050612449646,
            "question": "What is Rick Rubin's profession besides directing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rick Rubin directed the film Tougher Than Leather.",
            "html": "yago_4302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in Tougher Than Leather?",
            "html": "yago_4302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Tougher Than Leather released?",
            "html": "yago_4302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Rick Rubin direct?",
            "html": "yago_4302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4302_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because there are multiple documents that mention Rick Rubin's involvement with the film Tougher Than Leather. For example, in file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4302/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt, it says \"While he was working on the Licensed to Ill recording during the spring of 1986, I was finishing my senior thesis film at NYU. I wrote, produced, and directed a film entitled My Pal Satan. Rick liked it and provided me with some Slayer music as well as some Beastie Boys\u2019 music for the film's soundtrack.\" and then later on in file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4302/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt, it says \"In the fall of 1986 I was working with Rick Rubin, who was busy directing Tougher Than Leather. The single for \"Fight for Your Right\" was going crazy on the radio in New York as well as in other markets by November of 1986.\" \n\nThis suggests that Rick Rubin directed the film Tougher Than Leather."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Rick Rubin directed the film \"Tougher Than Leather\" (1988), which directly supports the statement that Rick Rubin directed the film Tougher Than Leather."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}